wobzy.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy Policy « Wobzy Premium Wordpress Themes

**Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is very important to us. We take care to protect the privacy of our clients and will do the same for all users of this web-site. This policy explains how we process information about site visitors and clients.

**Information safeguards**  
We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. We maintain strict security standards and procedures with a view to preventing unauthorised access to your data by anyone, including our staff. We use leading technologies such as (but not limited to) data encryption, firewalls and server authentication to protect the security of your data.

**Data Access & Corrections**  
Upon receipt of your written request, we will disclose to you your personal data held by us: we shall correct or delete inaccurate details. We regularly delete data which is no longer required.

**Changes to the website content and Privacy Policy**  
We may change the content or services found on our website at any time without notice, and consequently our Privacy Policy will be reviewed from time to time to take account of new laws and technologies, changes to our operations and practices and to make sure it remains appropriate to the changing environment. You agree to revisit this page regularly and your continued access to or use of the website will mean that you agree to the changes.

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies to monitor website user traffic patterns and site usage.  
Cookies are small pieces of text that a website transfers to the cookie file on your computer’s hard disk. Cookies enable users to navigate around the website and help us determine where you have been on the website, when you return to the website, where you came from, etc.  
Cookies cannot look into your computer and obtain information about you or your family or read any material kept on your hard drive.  
You can choose to disable cookies on your computer by changing your preferences and options in your browser. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to access some parts of our website.

**Hyperlinks**  
This website may contain hyperlinks or links to other sites, and other sites may link to our website. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by these websites.

**Monitoring**  
Please note that telephone conversations may be recorded.  
We may monitor our communications with our customers (including, but not limited to, phone conversations and emails) for legal, regulatory, quality assurance and training reasons.

**Important**  
By using this website and by submitting information to us via this website you give your consent that all your personal data collected by us via this website may be processed by us set out above.  
By submitting your personal details, you will be taken to have consented to this limited use of your personal data.  
You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing on-line over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default.
